我們的總統不僅服用精神藥物
We have a president who not only took mind-altering medication --
當美國艦隊與中國對峙時
a man who has his finger on the button
他可以隨時批准實施打擊
while U.S. Ships are squaring off with China --
還授意他的白宮顧問去干預...
but then instructed his White House counsel to coach a --
據稱  先生  沒有被證實
Allegedly, sir. Not proven.
去干預證人  他的做法
To coach a witness. Which is behavior either resulting
要麼是受藥物影響  要麼更糟
from the use of those drugs, or worse,
是有意想踐踏法律
a deliberate attempt to obstruct the law.
你不覺得兩種情況都該被彈劾嗎
Now wouldn't you call either scenario impeachable?
那該由國會決定  先生  而不是我
That's for the United States Congress to decide, sir. Not me.
你知道總統在服用任何藥物嗎
Were you aware that the president was taking any form of medication?
不  我不知道
No, I was not.
你注意到他舉止古怪嗎
Did you notice him acting in a bizarre fashion?
-情緒不穩  語無倫次  -沒有  先生
- Unstable, incoherent? - No, sir.
-有任何奇怪的行為嗎  -沒有  先生
- Any odd behavior? - No, sir.
在貿易戰之際解雇幕僚長不算嗎
Not even firing his chief of staff in the midst of a trade war?
他沒有解雇我  是我主動辭職的
He didn't fire me. I resigned.
你能告訴我們為什麼嗎
Would you tell us why?
我辭職是因為我覺得自己無法
I resigned because I felt I could no longer
再以最好的狀態為總統服務
serve the president to the best of my ability.
發生了什麼變化  是什麼讓你得出那樣的結論
And what changed? How did you come to that conclusion?
我與白宮中的某些人
I had some fundamental differences of opinion
基本理念不合
with certain people in the White House.
比如誰  總統嗎
Like who? The president?
不  先生
No, sir.
那某些人是指誰
Well, what certain people then?
實際上只有一個人
One person, actually.
副總統  弗蘭克·安德伍德
The vice president, Frank Underwood.
他想讓你離開嗎
He wanted you gone?
我不敢說副總統想怎麼樣  不想怎麼樣
I can't speak as to what the vice president did or didn't want.
他想要隱藏什麼嗎
Was he trying to hide anything?
他是不是怕你曝光什麼
Was he afraid you might expose something?
那你得去問他  先生
You'd have to ask him, sir.
司法委員會正在上演的是一齣鬧劇
What's happening in the Judiciary Committee is a farce.
共和黨正在利用這種...
The Republicans are exploiting the situ--
插一句  副總統先生
Excuse me, Mr. Vice President,
不僅僅是共和黨
but it's not just Republicans.
不少民主黨人也站出來說
A number of Democrats have come out saying
他們支持彈劾
they would support impeachment.
包括多數黨黨鞭  傑姬·夏普
Including the Majority Whip, Jackie Sharp.
這令人髮指
Which is egregious,
因為委員會還在進行聽證
since the committee hasn't stopped hearing testimony,
特別檢察官也沒有完成調查
and nor has the special prosecutor completed her investigation.
你極力維護總統
You vigorously defend the president,
但有報道稱你們已經鬧僵
but there are reports that you've had a falling out.
你們好幾個星期沒說過話了
That you haven't spoken in weeks.
一派胡言
That is simply not true.
我與白宮的高級官員通過話
I've spoken to senior staff at the White House
他說總統擔心你會在2016年大選中與他競爭
who say the president is worried you want to run against him in 2016.
而就在今天  琳達·瓦斯奎茲暗指你...
And just today Linda Vasquez intimated that you --
我相信總統一定會在2016年競選連任
Look, I fully expect that the president will run in 2016,
而且我希望他能夠慷慨地邀請我
and I hope he's generous enough to invite me
作他的競選夥伴
to be his running mate.
彈劾  定罪  如果是這個結果呢
Impeachment, conviction. Let's say it happens.
不會的  他完全是無辜的
It won't. He's completely innocent.
我們假設一下  你成了總統
Let's say it does happen. You become president.
我不會去想像那個情形
That is not a scenario I'm going to entertain.
但你腦中肯定有過這個想法
But the thought must have crossed your mind.
而且可以說  如果不是因為你
And one could make the argument that the president
總統也不會陷入這樣的窘境
wouldn't be in this predicament if it weren't for you.
是你的幕僚長與馮和拉尼根的牽連
It's your staff's involvement with Feng and Lanagin
才引發了鄧巴的調查
that expanded Dunbar's investigation,
-隨之發現了出行記錄  -這些彈劾聽證
- which resulted in the travel logs - Look, these impeachment hearings
是政治操縱的結果
are the result of political maneuvering,
-而不是  -是你在操縱還是共和黨
- not the fact that-- - Your maneuverings, or the Republicans?
莫裏  我一直很喜歡你  你的問題很尖銳
Morley, I've always liked you. You ask the tough questions.
你當然可以質疑我的判斷
And you can certainly question my judgment.
但不要質疑我的愛國心
But do not question my patriotism.
我為國家和總統服務  而不是我自己
I serve this nation and my president, not myself.
他滿口謊言
He's lying through his teeth.
我們所做的已經見效了
What we're doing is working.
讓大家一直私下談論
We keep the whisper campaign alive.
我們讓他顯得渴望權利  顯得奸詐
We spin him as power-hungry, as duplicitous.
將焦點集中在他身上  而不是您
Focus attention on him. Not you.
最新支持率是多少  20%嗎
What's the latest? 20%?
佐格比的數據是24%  您的講話起了作用
Zogby has you at 24. Your speech made a difference.
支持率正在上升
The approval numbers are moving in the right direction.
我們不能再這麼小打小鬧了
We need to do more than play the spin game.
我們要打垮弗蘭克  讓他而不是我去當犧牲品
We need to destroy Frank. Offer his head instead of mine.
-我們利用雷蒙德·塔斯克  -怎麼利用
- We use Raymond Tusk. - How?
在他的聽證會上  在他去司法委員會時
At his hearing. When he goes to the Judiciary.
先生  您已經被指控干預一個證人了
Sir, you're already being accused of coaching one witness.
如果您再干預另一...
If you take steps to coach anoth--
不是干預  是讓他說出事實
Not coaching. The truth.
雷蒙德承認洗錢
Raymond admits to the money laundering,
把弗蘭克推到風口浪尖  說我什麼都不知道
puts Frank at the center of this, and says I knew nothing.
之後我們會回報他的誠實
And then we'll reward him for his honesty.
您是說特赦嗎
You mean a pardon.
我想讓你跟他去談
I want you to talk to him.
讓我自己陷於危險之中嗎
And put myself at risk?
你現在不在政府供職了
Well, you're not part of this administration anymore.
沒有法律規定你不能去拜訪雷蒙德·塔斯克
There's no law that says you can't pay Raymond Tusk a visit.
作為回報  辭職也不非得永久有效  琳達
And in return, resignations don't have to last forever, Linda.
如果我這麼做  您得和我保持距離  越遠越好
If I do this, you have to be a million miles away.
特莉莎和我會去戴維營
Tricia and I'll go to Camp David.
不算特別遠  但也夠了
It's not a million miles away, but it'll do the job.
我可以對琳達下手  調查她的過去
I can go after Linda. Dig into her past --
搞定她解決不了大問題
Neutralizing her won't neutralize the bigger problem.
是總統想要我的命
It's the president that's after blood.
那他打算怎麼做
Then what's his move?
他不能要求我辭職  只能把我擠走
He can't ask me to resign. He'd have to force me out.
要擠走我的話  如果我是他
And to do that, if I were him,
肯定會回去找最初成就我的人
I would return to the hand that first fed me.
-雷蒙德·塔斯克嗎  -沒錯
- Raymond Tusk? - Exactly.
不會  他要是把你捲進去  他自己也難保
No, he'd have to implicate himself to implicate you.
除非他能得到赦免
Not if he gets a pardon.
這是唯一只有總統才能開出的條件
It's the one thing that only a president can offer.
塔斯克是個手榴彈  如果他赦免了他...
Tusk is a hand grenade. If he pardons him --
沒錯  塔斯克是個手榴彈
You're right. Tusk is a hand grenade,
我們得拽下保險栓  朝沃克扔過去
and we need to pull the pin and throw him at Walker
否則就是沃克拽下保險栓  扔向我們了
before Walker pulls the pin and throws him at us.
我得和雷蒙德見面  一對一
I want to meet with Raymond, one on one.
我代表你去談吧
Let me speak on your behalf.
-這樣的話  如果有人發現  -我瞭解雷蒙德
- That way if anyone finds -- -I know Raymond.
他只會對我做出回應
He won't respond to anyone but me.
他的聽證會安排在什麼時候
When's his hearing scheduled?
後天下午兩點
Uh, day after tomorrow. Two p.m.
-那我們還有40個小時行動  -是  先生
- That gives us 40 hours to make it happen. - Yes, sir.
翻譯  衛老哥
翻譯  某豚
翻譯  章魚X
翻譯  艾瑞卡
翻譯  冬麟
翻譯  香茗小焙
時間軸  吉吉
後期  餓得慌
特效  寶寶
顧問  老杜
校對  草草
總監  草草
紙牌屋
第二季  第十三集
人人影視傾情奉獻
可能是我的手機
I think it's mine.
賽斯  現在可是凌晨四點
Seth, it's four in the morning.
什麼時候
When?
我希望你跟她一起去
I want you to go with her.
-我這就去徵求洛克蘭的批准  -謝謝
- I'll get it cleared with Rockland right now. -Thank you.
密查姆說飛機30分鐘內就能準備好
Meechum says the plane will be ready in 30 minutes.
行  好
Okay, good.
你覺得只是恐慌癥發作
You think it was just a panic attack
-還是她真打算...  -我不知道
- or was she really trying -- -I don't know.
他們要她留院觀察一整夜就夠糟了
It was bad enough they felt they had to keep her overnight.
我給白宮醫生辦公室打個電話
I'm gonna call the White House physician's office,
-看看他們能不能推薦什麼人 -好
- see if they can recommend anyone. - Okay.
-等等  我的手機  -在你手裏
- Oh, wait. My phone. - It's in your hand.
我今晚回來
I'll be back sometime tonight.
彈劾是我們唯一的機會
Impeachment is our only chance.
這些席位在中期選舉中仍處於爭奪狀態
Here are the seats that are still in contention in the midterms.
這13個我們再怎麼努力也會失去
These 13 we're gonna lose no matter what we do.
但即便我們拿下剩下所有席位
But even if we win all the rest,
我們也只有五個席位的優勢
that only leaves us with a five-seat majority.
要麼保黨  要麼保總統
We either save the party or we save the president.
任何人反對彈劾的人
Anyone who votes against impeachment
在選舉前都會受到攻擊性廣告的攻擊
is gonna get pommeled by attack ads between now and election day.
你已經有多少票了
How many do you have already?
我們需要18票  我只有六票
We need 18. I have six.
那還要爭取12票
So, 12 more to go.
唐納德  我知道這是個很大的人情
Look, Donald, I know this is a big ask
你更想把注意力放在政策上  不...
and you prefer to focus on policy and not --
傑姬  不用說了  我加入
Jackie, you can stop. I'm on board.
-真的嗎  - 百分百
- Really? - 100%.
不得不說  我有點驚訝
I have to say I'm a little surprised.
你把那些手推車推進休息室的時候  你說
When you rolled those dollies into the cloakroom you said,
"跟我合作  我不是弗蘭克·安德伍德"
"Work with me. I'm not Frank Underwood."
然後你幫我通過了經濟刺激方案
And then you helped get my stimulus package through,
你信守了諾言
just like you promised.
這次你有什麼期望呢
And what do you expect this time?
我希望你永遠不會成為弗蘭克·安德伍德
That you never become Frank Underwood.
你要知道  如果我們成功了  他會取代沃克
You must realize if we're successful, he will replace Walker.
我不喜歡弗蘭克  但我更討厭成為少數黨
I don't like Frank. but I hate being in the minority even more.
我們不能讓共和黨同時執掌國會兩院
We can't let the Republicans control both houses of Congress.
我加入領導層以來  你變了
You've changed since I joined the leadership.
只是更懂得如何玩這場遊戲了
Just getting better at playing the game.
看來頑固不化這詞不太對
I guess you can teach an old liberal new tricks.
看來是的
I guess so.
告訴我你還需要誰
So, tell me who you still need.
我的律師說我贏得庭審的概率是一半一半
My lawyers are saying 50/50 that I survive a trial.
我不太滿意這個數字
Now, I'm not a big fan of those odds,
但我願意接受
but I'm willing to take 'em.
如果你的律師說這事就看運氣
If your lawyers are putting it at a coin toss,
那你是花錢雇了一群太過樂觀的人
then you're paying them too much to be overly optimistic.
我怎麼能信任加勒特
And how can I trust Garrett?
他背叛了20年的友誼
He turned his back on 20 years of friendship.
他也可以這麼說你
He could accuse you of the same.
這地球上沒有人
Well, nobody on this planet
比我更想看弗蘭克·安德伍德進監獄了
wants to see Frank Underwood go to jail more than I do.
我只是不想到時跟他關在一起
I just don't want to be sharing a cell with him.
這種事不會發生的
That won't happen.
你只給了我加勒特的口頭承諾
All you've given me to go on is Garrett's word.
他想讓你說出實情
He's asking you to tell the truth.
做正確的事的人必有好報
Good things happen to those who do the right thing.
你們就指望弗蘭克會跪地求饒
And you just expect Frank to lie down,
舉旗認輸嗎
throw in the towel, hmm?
連求饒的機會也不給他
We don't even give him the chance.
你的證詞會讓他全無反擊之力
Your testimony knocks him out cold.
請稍等
Excuse me.
什麼事  啊  多謝你
Yes? Oh, thank you.
請等一下
Hold on.
給你
There you go.
普契尼歌劇
蝴蝶夫人
我妻子送的小禮物
Care package from my wife.
那麼  請繼續
Now, you were saying.
我得提醒你一下  她現在完全不在狀態
I just want to warn you, she's not herself right now.
他們不得不給她服用了大劑量的藥物
They had to put her on some heavy doses.
什麼藥
Of what?
主要是碳酸鋰[抗躁狂藥]
Lithium, mostly.
不然就得留院觀察30天了
It was either that or commit her for 30 days.
她剛吃了藥  可能有點...
Now she just took some, so she might be a little...
梅根
Megan?
別碰我
Stop.
你媽媽告訴我他們從湖裏救起了你
Your mom told me they found you in the lake.
你管我呢
What do you care?
我非常關心你
I care very much.
才怪
No, you don't.
沒人會利用他們關心的人
You don't use somebody you care about.
娼妓
Whore.
蕩婦
Slut.
婊子
Bitch.
叛徒
Traitor.
他們就是這麼說我的
That's what they call me.
發郵件  在網上
In my mail. Online.
真希望我沒打那通電話
I wish I'd never called.
真希望我沒見過你
I wish I'd never met you.
你說什麼我信什麼  真是蠢透了
I feel so stupid believing what you told me.
我還以為你真心關心我
Thinking that you did care.
我本來都快恢復了
I was getting better.
這全怨你
You did this to me.
我每吃一片藥  都會想到他
Every time I take one of these I think of him.
接下來我想到的
And the next face I think of?
就是你
It's yours.
你覺得被利用了  我很遺憾
I'm sorry that you felt used.
我沒有利用你
You weren't.
我只是
I just, um...
就像我說的  政治風向變了  而且
like I told you, the political landscape shifted and --
而我們發現
and we found...
梅根
Megan?
你好
Hello?
我收到你的短信了
I got your text.
我知道我不該聯繫你  但我覺得
I know I shouldn't be reaching out to you, but I thought...
不  沒關係  我很高興你通知了我
No, that doesn't matter. I'm glad you did.
她怎麼樣
How is she?
狀態很不好
In bad shape.
說實話我很吃驚他們還敢讓她離開醫院
I'm surprised they even let her out of the hospital, to be honest.
有什麼我能做的嗎
Is there anything I can do?
用不用我聯繫她的親人  親自去探望她
Should I contact her family or go out there myself?
我們最好不要打擾她了
We should probably leave her alone.
你還好嗎
Are you okay?
我沒事  你呢
I'm fine. How about you?
還撐得住
Uh, holding up.
和律師商量了一整天
Spent the whole day talking to lawyers.
這對孩子們太不容易了
It's hard on the kids.
他們既窘迫又害怕
They're embarrassed and frightened.
但我們會熬過去的
But we'll get through it.
我覺得你和加勒特的講話很感人
I thought the speech you and Garrett gave was very moving.
似乎起了點作用
Well, it seems to have helped some.
其實我是受你的啟發
I was inspired by you, actually.
你敢於在電視上承認墮過胎
When you admitted to the abortion on TV.
真相往往很有衝擊力
The truth is a powerful thing.
特莉莎  我想向你道歉
Tricia, I want to apologize.
為什麼
What for?
你的家庭所經歷的這些變故
I feel partly responsible for everything
我覺得我有一部分責任
your family's going through.
是我建議你們去見咨詢師
It was my suggestion that you get counseling.
早知今日  我當初就什麼都不會說了
And had I known then, I never would have said a word.
克萊爾  別這麼說  見咨詢師效果很好
Claire, please. Counseling was a godsend.
加勒特和我需要幫助
Garrett and I needed help,
而且也確實起了作用
and it's made things better.
我應該感謝你
I should be thanking you.
還要感謝你把梅根的事告訴我
And thank you for letting me know about Megan.
你能去看她  真是好心
It was kind of you to make that trip.
你是個好人  克萊爾
You're a good person, Claire.
保重
Be well.
我估計你是想說聽證會的事
I take it this is about my hearing.
是不是沃克聯繫過你了
Did Walker get to you first?
沒比你快多少
Barely.
但有時候  哪怕只快一點也足夠了
But sometimes barely is enough.
他肯定提出給你特赦
I'm sure he offered you a pardon.
提供競爭對手給不了的  才是高招
Always better to offer something your competitor can't.
但我能給你更好的
Oh, but I can.
據我所知  憲法規定的
The last time I read the Constitution,
副總統能給的最有價值的東西也就是...
the most a vice president could offer was, um,
陪陪笑臉  遞遞眼色了
smile and a wink.
我想我已經證明我不是一般的副總統
I think I've proven that I'm not your typical vice president.
一般或不一般  你都輸了  弗蘭克
Typical or not, you've lost, Frank.
我還有出路  你沒有
I have an out. You don't.
加勒特撐不過彈劾的
Garrett will not survive impeachment.
你絕不能否認
If there's one skill you can't deny,
我拉選票的能力
it's my ability to whip votes.
那是在眾議院  不是在參議院
In the House. Not in the Senate.
但依據憲法  我是參議院的主席
Which the Constitution makes me the President of.
你也看到我是怎麼通過福利改革了
And you saw what I did with entitlement.
傲慢使你自以為了不起了  弗蘭克
Hubris is giving you delusions of grandeur, Frank.
就算沃克僥倖逃過一劫
Let's say Walker squeaks by.
是的  你能得到特赦
Yes, you get your pardon.
但你卻把自己跟一個
But you've bound yourself at the hip
沒有任何政治資本的人拴在一起了
to a man who has zero political capital.
如果他被定罪  我們都要坐牢
And if he gets convicted, we all go to jail.
誰都沒有特赦了
There's no pardon for anyone.
我願意賭一把
I'll roll the dice.
雷蒙德  用你的商業頭腦想想
Raymond, think like a businessman.
你不就是靠盡量減小風險積累財富的嗎
Haven't you built a fortune by minimizing risk?
這不就是你這些年用錢堆砌國會
Isn't that why you stacked Congress all these years,
引領加勒特當上總統
why you guided Garrett to the Oval,
留我當黨鞭的原因嗎
and why you kept me on as Whip?
沃克是個垃圾股  貶值得快
Walker is a junk bond quickly depreciating,
而我可以迅速解決和中國的貿易戰
whereas I can end the conflict with China
還能保你不坐牢
and keep you in the black.
你沒法保證改善和中國的關係
You can't promise better relations with China.
我破壞的  我也能修復
I wrecked them. I can repair them.
一起合作吧  就如我們起初打算的那樣
Now let's work together, as we always intended to do.
等你被關進棺材大的牢房裏
When they put you in that box barely bigger than a coffin,
記住今晚這美妙的音樂吧
remember how beautiful the music was tonight.
或許能讓你稍微好受點
It might give you some small degree of comfort.
普契尼太傷感  我喜歡積極向上的
Puccini's a downer. I prefer something much more optimistic.
他們不肯放布朗  審判日期已經定了
They won't touch Brown. The trial date is set.
他們可以減少指控
They can reduce the charges.
達拉斯不願讓步  如果我繼續施壓
Dallas won't give. If I keep pressing,
會顯得可疑
it'll start to look suspect.
我能確保你不被起訴
What I can do is make sure you don't get prosecuted.
還有我不再替你工作
And I stop working for you.
不全是  我跟檢察官說
Not quite. I told the U.S. Attorney
我們想讓你為我們工作
that we wanted to bring you on with us.
網絡恐怖主義分局  你的案底將一筆勾銷
Cyber terrorism division. You'd get a clean slate, as --
門都沒有
No fucking way.
他們不會就那麼放棄你
They're not gonna let your case go
除非我們給他們充分的理由
unless we give them a compelling reason.
-沒別的  -我跟調查局鬥爭了半輩子
- There's no o - I've spent half my life fighting the Bureau.
我只能這麼說
It's the only way I could sell it.
抓住機會  嘉文
Take this opportunity, Gavin,
趁他們還沒改主意
before they change their minds.
我要見道格拉斯·斯坦普
I want to meet with Douglas Stamper.
不行  我們說好了我幫你找出路
No. The deal was I find you a way out.
說好的是你幫布朗脫身並且還我自由
No, the deal was you help out Brown and you give me my freedom.
你沒為布朗辦成任何事
You haven't done shit for Brown,
還想繼續控制我
and you still want to keep me under your thumb.
讓我見斯坦普  否則一切免談
So I meet Stamper, or any kinda deal is off.
雷蒙德沒答應
Raymond said no.
他沒表態
He said neither yes nor no.
我會繼續施壓
I'll keep the pressure on.
他還是有可能指證你
So he could still name you.
是的  一切皆有可能
He could. Anything's possible.
你得阻止他
Well, you have to stop him.
我在嘗試
I'm trying.
嘗試遠遠不夠  弗蘭西斯
Well, trying's not enough, Francis.
我總不能在聽證會上坐在他旁邊
Well, I can't sit next to him in the hearing room
拿槍抵著他頭
with a gun to his head.
這聽起來像在找借口
Now that sounds like an excuse.
事實就是這樣
It's a reality.
你答應過  我不用做最壞的打算
You promised me I wasn't going to have to prepare for the worst.
我也打算信守諾言
And I intend to keep that promise.
我想確保  我們都要確定會沒事
Well, I want to be sure. I want both of us to be sure.
唯一萬無一失的辦法  就是讓沃克阻止他
The only surefire way is for Walker to call him off personally.
那就去辦
Then make that happen.
我不能逼一個拿我當敵人的人
I cannot force a man who thinks I'm his enemy
突然把我當朋友
to suddenly call me his friend.
我該做的都做了
I've done what I had to do.
現在輪到你了
Now you do what you have to do.
勾引他  把你的心交給他
Seduce him. Give him your heart.
挖出來放在他手上
Cut it out and put it in his fucking hands.
親愛的總統先生
Dear Mr. President,
我正在用我離開桑蒂諾時
I'm writing on an Underwood portable
我父親給我的安德伍德打字機給您寫信
my father gave me when I left for the Sentinel.
我父親將它給我時說了些話
It was the words my father said when he gave it to me
安德伍德國際
比這台七十多年的機器更讓我能產生共鳴
that have resonated even more than this 70-year-old machine.
安德伍德國際
"這個安德伍德建立了一個商業帝國"他說
"This Underwood built an empire," He said.
"現在該你去建立一個屬於你自己的帝國了"
"Now you go and build one of your own."
這些話一直激勵著我
Those words have been a large part of what has motivated my life.
我只用這台打字機寫過另一封信
I've only written one other letter with these keys.
那封信不辱使命  希望這次也一樣
It did not fail me then. I hope it will not fail me now.
您說我想削弱您
You said I wanted to diminish you.
實際上  我沒有
The truth is, I don't.
您說我想在2016年跟您競爭
You said I wanted to challenge you in 2016.
實際上  我沒有
The truth is, I don't.
您說我想自己當總統
You said I wanted the presidency for myself.
實際上
The truth is,
我的確想
I do.
哪個政客沒想過
What politician hasn't dreamed about what it would be like
戴維營
宣誓執掌國家最高權力
to take the oath of the highest office of our land?
戴維營
我曾盯著您的總統辦公桌看  覬覦它
I've stared at your desk in the Oval and coveted it.
權力  威望
The power, the prestige.
那些東西對我這樣一個來自南卡羅來納州
Those things have a strong pull on someone like me,
一座小鎮  曾一無所有的人來說有致命的吸引力
who came from a small South Carolina town with nothing.
但自您就職時起
But since you assumed office,
我唯一的目標就是為您而戰
my only aim has been to fight for you
與您並肩作戰
and alongside you,
無論是在國會還是現在
whether that be in Congress or as now,
在這場彈劾之戰中
the battle over impeachment.
或許有一天  我有幸能成為總統
Maybe one day I'll have my chance to serve as president,
但絕不是您在任期間
but not while you are the nation's leader.
在您身上  我看到了勇敢
And in you, sir, I see a brave man.
看到了正直  您是我願意永遠追隨的總統
A just man. A president whom I would follow anywhere,
無論我們遇到多大的阻力
no matter how strong the wind blows against us.
有一件事我從沒對任何人說過
I want to tell you something I have never told anyone:
我13歲那年在穀倉裏撞見我父親
When I was 13 I walked in on my father in the barn.
他把獵槍伸到嘴裏
There was a shotgun in his mouth.
他朝我擺了擺手說道"過來  弗蘭西斯
He waved me over. "Come here, Francis," He said.
替我扣動扳機"
"Pull the trigger for me."
因為他沒有勇氣自己做
Because he didn't have the courage to do it himself.
我說"不  爸爸"  就離開了
I said, "No, Papa," And walked out,
我知道他永遠沒有那個勇氣
knowing he would never find that courage.
接下來的七年裏  我父親生不如死
The next seven years were hell for my father,
但我母親和我更加痛苦
but even more hell for my mother and me.
他令我們都苦不堪言
He made all of us miserable.
酗酒  絕望  暴力
Drinking, despair, violence.
我一生中唯一的後悔  就是當時沒扣動扳機
My only regret in life is that I didn't pull that trigger.
死亡對他來說會是種解脫
He would have been better off in the grave,
沒有他我們也會過得更好
and we would have been better off without him.
我不會讓您陷入同樣的境地
I'm not going to put you in the same position
像我父親對我那樣
as my father put me in.
信中附上了一張紙
You will find enclosed on a separate sheet
上面供認了所有您被指控的罪名
a confession to the crimes you have been accused of.
都是假的  但我的簽名會使它們成真
They're false words, but my signature will make them true.
有必要的話就用吧
Use them if you must.
如果您真的認為我的所作所為都是為了自己
If you truly believe that I have only served myself,
那麼我已經永遠失去了您的信任
then I have forever lost your trust.
我現在能做的  只有獻出自己的自由以保住您
All I can do now is give you my freedom to save your own.
我說過我會替您承擔責任
I said I would take the fall for you,
現在我把方法告訴了您
and now I give you the means to make that happen.
我要自己扣動扳機
I am pulling the trigger myself.
為了實現夢想我們都要做出犧牲
We all must make sacrifices to achieve our dream,
但有時為了大局必須犧牲自己
but sometimes we must sacrifice ourselves for the greater good.
做出這樣的犧牲是我的榮幸
It is my honor to make such a sacrifice now.
您忠實的朋友  至少我仍這樣認為
Your loyal friend, still in my heart,
即便您不這麼想  弗蘭西斯
if not in yours, Francis.
憲法列出了一般原則
The Constitution sets forth the general principles --
先生  總統的電話
Sir? The president's on the phone.
總統先生
Mr. President.
我收到信了  我讓特莉莎也看了
I got your letter. I had Tricia read it, too.
我很糾結  弗蘭克  一半認為你是懇誠的
I'm torn, Frank. Half of me wants to think you're genuine.
另一半卻一個字也不信
The other half doesn't trust a word of it.
特莉莎也這麼想嗎
Does Tricia feel the same way?
她信任克萊爾  所以她也想相信你
She believes in Claire, which inclines her to believe in you.
我字字發自肺腑
I meant every syllable.
我想讓您百分之百地相信
I wanted you to know beyond a shadow of a doubt
我願做任何必要的事
that I am willing to do whatever is necessary.
那麼  我為什麼拋不開疑慮呢
Well, then why can't I shake the shadow?
因為我是個騙子  先生
Because I'm a liar, sir.
因為我無所顧忌  甚至可以說沒有同情心
Because I lack scruples and some would even say compassion.
但那只是我展示給世人的一面
But that's just the image that I present to the world
因為那能使人害怕  讓人尊敬我
because it elicits fear and respect.
但我不是那樣的人
But it is not who I am.
我希望我的信能向您證明這一點
My hope was that my letter would prove that to you.
好吧  就算你說的都是真的
Well, even if you are being genuine,
對我也沒什麼用
that doesn't do much for me.
我想躲過彈劾
I won't survive impeachment
不能只靠我和我的副總統關繫好
because I got along with my vice president.
是啊  我同意  您需要的不只是我的好意
No, I agree you need more than my good intentions.
證明給我看  弗蘭克
Proof. That's what I want to see, Frank.
別光承擔責任  我要結果
And not just falling on the sword. Show me results.
那樣我會重新考慮你是否值得信任
And then I'll reconsider whether you're worth any of my trust at all.
您是說投票
You're talking votes.
是的  拉票是你的強項
Yeah. Whipping votes was your strong suit.
我想看到你那一面
That's the side of you I want to see.
我已經開始著手了  先生
I've already begun, sir.
是嗎  得到票數了嗎
Yeah? You have a count?
只有個大概  形勢一直在變化
An approximation. The sands keep shifting.
我們能得到眾議院的支持嗎
Well, can we survive the House or not?
有可能  但是傑姬·夏普在阻撓
Possibly, but Jackie Sharp is making it very difficult.
告訴我票數
Give me numbers.
她需要18票  已經拉到過半
Over half of the 18 that she needs,
所以我想從參議院下手
which is why I'd like to start focusing on the Senate.
你不覺得現在行動有點早嗎
Don't you think that's premature?
我們必須有所準備
We should be prepared.
重中之重就是確保您不被定罪
The key battle is making sure that you avoid conviction.
你繼續拉票  有消息告訴我
Well, you keep whipping, you keep getting me information,
我就等你電話了
I'll answer your calls.
但別以為你我就此相安無事了  弗蘭克
But don't take that as a sign of reconciliation, Frank.
我會感激收穫  先生
I'll sing for my supper, sir.
但我不會以為我能不勞而獲
I don't expect it for free.
我們明早再商量
Let's talk again tomorrow.
謝謝您  總統先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
你說你想有選擇餘地
You said you wanted options.
但弗蘭克讓我沒得選  他坑了我
Frank didn't leave me options. He fucked me.
是你和塔斯克沆瀣一氣  先把他坑了
You fucked him first when you sided with Tusk.
但誰管中間過程怎樣
But who cares what happened each inning?
只有最終比分才算數
It's the final score that counts.
我在他麾下八年  為他跑前跑後
Eight years I spent busting my ass in this office.
看來還是躲不過為他賣命
I can't seem to escape it.
你是幫我們還是不幫
You gonna help us or not?
我要知道我有什麼好處
I need to know what I gain.
-你會得到關照的  -說具體點
- You'll be taking care of. - Specifically.
等到塵埃落定  再看看要怎麼辦吧
We'll see what makes sense when all the chips have fallen.
那你是要我悶頭往懸崖下跳
So you just want me to leap off a cliff
指望著運氣好摔不死嗎
and hope for a soft landing beneath?
現在誰都不會要你  除了我們
No one will touch you now. Nobody except us.
我們就是你最好的運氣
We're as soft as you're gonna get.
能在白宮給我一官半職嗎
A job at the White House?
這我說不准
No promises.
結果如何取決於你的
Other than something commensurate
忠誠度和經驗
with your loyalty and experience.
我完全可以就此抽身  開始新的生活
I could just walk away from it all. Start a new life.
你抽不了身  你知道你做不到
No, you can't. You know you can't.
離了國會山  你只會衰萎
You'd wither away anywhere but the Hill.
不管你怎麼騙自己
It's never been about the money,
你做這一行不是為了錢
no matter what you tell yourself.
我跳槽的時候  弗蘭克求我留下
When I left, Frank begged me to stay.
他說"這是權和錢二選一"
"Power versus money," He said.
別屈尊加入那些繳富人稅的人
Don't reduce myself to a tax bracket.
他說得對  但我不認為他會求你
He was right. And I doubt he begged.
他對了一半
He was half right.
只要有權力握在手裏  就比錢有用
Power is better than money for as long as it lasts.
但權力總會滑出手心
But it never lasts.
你的回答是什麼
What's your answer?
你當了黨鞭之後變得更冷血了
You've gotten colder since you've taken over this job.
這樣辦事容易些
It makes things easier.
只是對外嗎
On the outside.
內外皆是
And the inside.
我想你  傑姬
I miss you, Jackie.
你打算合作的話  就告訴我
Tell me if you'll cooperate.
你哥哥在議員手下幹得如何
How's your brother enjoying working with the congressman?
我接個電話
Oh, excuse me one second.
總統先生
Mr. President.
我要你打給塔斯克  告訴他交易取消
I want you to call Tusk. Tell him the deal is off.
-什麼  -你說得對
- What? - You were right.
我不想冒此風險
I don't want to take the risk.
但我已經和他談過了
But I already spoke to him.
那就再和他談談  告訴他特赦沒戲了
Well, so speak to him again. And tell him there's no pardon.
先生  我起初對這策略確實有些懷疑
Sir, I -- I -- I was skeptical of this strategy at first,
但我們已經選了這條路  就該走到底
but now that we've gone down this road, we should stick to it.
琳達  你還想回來做幕僚長嗎
Linda, do you still want your job back?
當然  先生
Of course, sir.
那就打給他
Then make the call.
我想先看看眾議院的結果
I'd rather see what happens in the House
再決定要不要幫你們
before I get involved in any way.
但如果你能表現出對總統堅定的支持
But if you came out vigorously in defense of the President,
可能會讓司法委員會覺得...
it might convince the Judiciary Committee --
說實話  我並不是很想
To be honest, I'm not particularly inclined
幫沃克的忙
to be doing Walker any favors.
邁克爾  我知道他撤銷了你的國務卿提名
Now, Michael, I know he revoked your nomination.
他完全沒有為我爭取
He didn't fight for me at all.
他那時剛剛當選  還沒有足夠的...
Well, he'd just been elected. He wasn't in a position to --
才怪  他明明有這權力
Wrong. He had a clear mandate.
他完全可以支持我
He was in a strong position to defend me.
你說得對
You're right.
如果我是總統  我不會那麼輕易放棄
If I had been President I wouldn't have given in so easily.
我會在那篇文章曝光後堅定支持你
I would've stuck by you after that article came to light.
老實說  如果國務卿是你而不是杜蘭特
In fact, if you'd been our secretary of state instead of Durant,
我們和中國的關係或許就不會這麼差了
I don't think we'd be in the mess we are with China.
但事實是  如果換了我
But the truth is, I wouldn't have
我也不會提名你做國務卿
nominated you for secretary of state in the first place.
我會提名你做財政部長
I would have nominated you for secretary of treasury.
因為你在經濟領域的專業知識
Because your expertise in economics is
比你的外交知識強得多
even better than your grasp on foreign affairs.
如果我是總統  你就會做財政部長
No, if I were president, you'd be secretary of treasury.
如果你是總統...
If you were president.
沒錯
That's right.
你不能這樣
You can't do this.
怎麼回事
What happened?
是弗蘭克搗的鬼嗎
Was it Frank?
琳達  聽我說
Linda, listen to me --
我明白
I understand.
謝謝你
Thanks.
交易取消了
The deal is off.
她說原因了嗎
Did she say why?
沒有  只說他改主意了
No. Other than he changed his mind.
但肯定是因為弗蘭克
But it must be Frank.
我們還是按原計劃來
Then we go back to the original plan.
沒錯  和以前一樣拒不解釋
That's right. You plead the Fifth just like you did before.
這就是出政治鬧劇
This is political theater.
-我們可以矇混過關然後關注  -天吶
- We get past it and focus on the - Jesus Christ.
怎麼了
What is it?
雷米·丹頓自願去鄧巴那裏作證  就是現在
Remy Danton is volunteering to testify to Dunbar, right now.
他自願的  不是被傳喚的嗎
He volunteered? He wasn't subpoenaed?
看起來是的
Looks that way.
他要出賣我
He's gonna sell me out.
那樣的話他也會遭到起訴
That would open him up to prosecution.
除非他受到了保護
Unless he's being protected.
丹頓在哪
Where's Danton?
我給他助理打電話
I'll call his assistant.
你是否促成外資
Did you or did you not facilitate foreign money
流入政治行動委員會
being funneled into political action committees?
根據我律師的意見
On the advice of my counsel,
我保留行使第五修正案的權利
I reserve my right to invoke the Fifth Amendment.
馮山德聲稱你不僅是促成了此事
Xander Feng claims you not only facilitated,
更是最初的策劃者
you orchestrated the scheme.
你如何回應這項證詞
Now what is your response to that testimony?
根據我律師的意見  我保留我的權利
On the advice of my counsel, I reserve my right to --
你今天可以一直保留你的權利  塔斯克先生
You can reserve your right all day long, Mr. Tusk.
但等你面對陪審團時
But when you appear in front of a grand jury,
我確信司法部門一定會起訴你
as I'm sure the Justice Department intends,
你的沉默將使你垮台
your silence will be your downfall.
議員有問題要問嗎
Does the congressman have a question?
你可以躲著我們  先生
You can hide from us all you want, sir.
卻躲不過與你平起平坐的陪審團
You cannot hide from a jury of your peers.
-主席先生  -就這樣吧  我說完了
- Mr. Chairman. - That's it. I'm done.
我放棄我剩餘的時間
I relinquish the remainder of my time.
下面交給田納西州女議員
The chair recognizes the congresswoman from Tennessee.
12分鐘  女士
You have 12 minutes, ma'am.
塔斯克先生  我們捲入了與中國的貿易戰中
Mr. Tusk, our nation is currently embroiled in a trade war with China.
這嚴重挫傷了我國經濟
It has gutted our economy.
使我們的海軍處於險境
It has placed our navy in harm's way.
-而使我們陷入這困境的總統  -他知道
- The president who put us there has -- He knew.
你說什麼
Excuse me?
我的委託人保留
My client reserves the --
他知道  你們不就是想知道這個嗎
He knew. Isn't that what you're all wondering?
請安靜
Quiet, please.
知道什麼  確切一些
Knew what, exactly?
有一套機制  它在過去10年裏
There was a mechanism by which a great many contributions
貢獻了大量的捐助款
were made over the last 10 years.
我仍然認為
The legality of this mechanism is something
這套機制並不觸犯法律
that I continue to believe is within the boundaries of the law.
但至於該機制本身  馮山德先生說得對
But as for the mechanism itself, Mr. Feng is correct.
是我策劃的  是我促成的
I orchestrated it. I facilitated it.
總統是知道的
And the president knew about it.
丹頓剛剛取消了
Danton just canceled.
去他的吧  我們有塔斯克
Screw Danton. We've got Tusk.
接通司法部長
Get me the attorney general.
沒有這個必要  塔斯克先生
That won't be necessary, Mr. Tusk.
請和我們走一趟
If you'll come with us.
真可惜
That's a shame.
手銬也是我遺願清單中的一項呢
Handcuffs were another item on my bucket list.
這邊走  先生  你有權保持沉默
Right this way, sir. You have the right to remain silent.
你所說的一切將用來作為控告你的證據
Anything you say can and will be used against you.
我們談談條件吧  他在聽證會上很配合
We'll want a bond. For his cooperation in the hearing.
認罪了再談條件
I'll talk bonds if you'll talk a plea.
人們對證詞的反應又快又強烈
Response to the testimony has been swift and vocal.
白宮觀察
華盛頓爆發抗議  沃克總統未表態
抗議者從昨天起
Protesters have been gathering in front of
便聚集在白宮前
the White House since yesterday,
要求沃克總統下台
demanding President Walker's resignation.
一份網上請願書在過去24小時裏
And an online petition has already accumulated
已經獲得二十多萬人簽名
over 200,000 signatures in the past 24 hours.
梅傑·加勒特
CBS新聞網首席白宮記者
兩院公開譴責總統的人數
The list of lawmakers publicly condemning the president
越來越多
has grown on both sides of the aisle.
今天下午  中國大使
And this afternoon the Chinese ambassador
也譴責了沃克政府
also condemned the Walker administration,
指責其瞞著北京與腐敗商人做交易
saying China would not negotiate with a president
他說中國不會與這樣的總統進行談判
who dealt with corrupt businessmen behind Beijing's back.
如今  兩國的軍艦
This at a time when warships from both countries --
白宮觀察
華盛頓爆發抗議  沃克總統未表態
與此同時  總統與第一夫人
Meanwhile the president and first lady
仍在戴維營閉門不出  尚未對華盛頓
remain bunkered at Camp David and have offered no public response
最新的進展發表公開回應
to the most recent developments in Washington.
我們請到了《華爾街電訊報》的艾拉·薩伊德
I'm here with Ayla Sayyad of the Wall Street Telegraph.
斯科特·瑟曼
ABC七台新聞組
艾拉·薩伊德
《華爾街電訊報》
艾拉  我必須先說
And Ayla, I have to begin by saying that sources
斯科特·瑟曼
ABC七台新聞組
據國會知情人士透露
on the Hill are telling me
司法委員會可能完全跳過辯論
that the Judiciary Committee may bypass debate all together.
斯科特·瑟曼
ABC七台新聞組
艾拉·薩伊德
《華爾街電訊報》
不  委員會還沒有人正式發表這樣的聲明
Uh, no one on the committee has gone on record about that.
但如果不是委員會十分傾向於
But do you think these rumors would be circulating
建議眾議院啟動彈劾程序
if there weren't some sort of strong preference
也不會有這種傳言了吧
to recommend the Articles of Impeachment to the House?
艾拉·薩伊德
《華爾街電訊報》
我認為幾乎可以肯定彈劾很受支持
I think it's safe to assume there is strong support.
我看到的每份民調都顯示
Every poll I've seen shows
很大一部分美國人希望更進一步
an overwhelming majority of Americans want this to move forward.
斯科特·瑟曼
ABC七台新聞組
艾拉·薩伊德
《華爾街電訊報》
我覺得政客們不會無視這一點
I don't think politicians are going to ignore that.
我已經和我的一些同事聊過了
I've talked to a number of my colleagues already.
民主黨這邊有些支持者
There's support on my side of the aisle.
-你有多少  -現在包括我在內有五個
- Well, how many do you have? - Five at this point, including me.
那就一共有60個了  還需要七個
That would put us at 60. We'd still need seven more.
你也看了昨晚的民調了
You've seen the overnight polls.
他的支持率都降到個位數了
He's dipped down into the single digits.
你想和我們一起發表公開聲明嗎
Are you willing to make a public statement with us?
我覺得事到如今
I think the country could use
兩黨合作一下也不是壞事吧
a little bipartisanship right now, don't you?
你覺得他們在虛張聲勢嗎
Do you think they're bluffing?
為了動搖參議院那些仍在猶豫的人而耍的花招
That it's some sort of stunt to sway the undecideds in the Senate?
邁克爾·科恩小氣又記仇  先生
Michael Kern is bitter and small-minded, sir,
但如果他們沒獲得足夠的支持
but he wouldn't appear publicly with Mendoza
他不會和門多薩一同公開表態
if they didn't have the numbers.
可以想像眾議院的情況比之前更糟了
Well, I imagine we're worse off in the House than we were before.
其實我本來和傑姬·夏普聊得還挺有成效
In fact, I had a very productive conversation with Jackie Sharp.
她同意停止攻擊
She agreed to stop the attack
只要我們在中期選舉後支持她做多數黨領袖
if we give her our support for majority leader after the midterms.
但雷蒙德一提供他的證詞
But once Raymond gave his testimony,
她就打電話說交易取消
she called to say the deal was off.
雷蒙德真的給了我們很大打擊
Raymond really has set us back.
我真想不通他為什麼要撒謊
I can't fathom why he lied.
他要報復我
Well, it's retribution.
-為了什麼  能源危機嗎  -不是
- For what? The energy crisis? - No.
您給了他什麼好處嗎
Did you offer him something?
雷蒙德的證詞確實於我們不利
Well, Raymond's testimony hurts,
但並沒有終結我們
but it can't finish us off.
謊言是無法證明的
It's impossible to prove a lie.
彈劾不可避免
Impeachment is inevitable.
現在民眾輿論成了敵人  事實已經不重要了
Public opinion is the adversary now. Facts no longer matter.
您應該給科恩打個電話  跟他本人聊聊
You should give Kern a call. The personal touch.
如果他重新支持我們
If he came back to us,
別的民主黨可能就會膽怯退縮
it might make the other Democrats get cold feet.
中國也在幫倒忙
Well, China isn't helping.
錢主席不回我的電話
President Qian won't return my calls.
北京那邊肯定覺得我氣數已盡
Beijing must smell death.
他們只是在利用這個局面尋求籌碼
They're just exploiting the situation for leverage.
現在先別考慮中國
Let's not worry about China for the moment.
一步一步慢慢來  先生
One battle at a time, sir.
我大概是完了  弗蘭克
Maybe I'm finished, Frank.
也許我該接受  我們沒法全身而退了
Maybe I need to start accepting that we won't pull out of this.
總統先生  我知道您累了
Mr. President, I know you're tired.
我知道這一切讓您備受折磨
I know this has been hell for you.
確實  彈劾會是個嚴重的打擊
And, yes, impeachment would be an awful blow.
我們要在參議院浴血奮戰了
We'd have to fight tooth and nail in the Senate.
確實  我們將不得不哀求和妥協
And, yes, we'll have to beg and compromise
重新賺回我們的政治資本
to regain our political capital.
但我們一定會勝利  先生
But we have it in us, sir.
不管拼得多麼頭破血流
No matter how many scars it leaves us with.
不僅僅是我們  弗蘭克
It's not just us, Frank.
還有特莉莎  還有我的孩子們
It's Tricia. It's my children.
我整夜失眠  想著他們看到父親退縮
I stay awake at night, thinking how much it would crush them,
將是多大的打擊
seeing their father hauled off.
先生  不會那樣的  我不會允許
Sir, that won't happen because I won't let it.
如果我們遇上最糟的情況
If we're confronted by the worst,
我至少會確保您不會遭受牢獄之災
I'll make sure you never step foot behind bars.
我向您保證
You have my word on that.
他現在身處黑暗
He's in the darkness now.
我是唯一指路的明燈
And I'm the only beacon of light.
現在只要溫柔地把他引向礁石就可以了
Now we gently guide him toward the rocks.
總統先生  您還有我的信
Mr. President, you also still have my letter.
如果您想走那條路  現在還不算太晚
It's not too late, if you want to use that option.
不  你留在國會比待在監獄更有用
No, you're more useful to me on the Hill than in handcuffs.
我會給科恩打電話
I'll call Kern.
-晚安  先生  -晚安
- Goodnight, sir. - Night.
格林告訴你多少
How much did Green tell you?
足夠讓我現身
Enough that I showed up.
他大概沒提到瑞秋·波斯納  是吧
He probably didn't mention Rachel Posner, huh?
別擔心  他不知道
Don't worry. He doesn't know.
但我知道
I do.
你把她藏在喬帕的一間公寓裏
You have her in an apartment in Joppa.
我知道你的一舉一動
I have your movements.
你有你毀掉手機之前的短信
I have your text messages before you destroyed your phone.
不過這已經足夠了
But that's more than enough.
我相信很多人都很想知道她知道的事
I'll bet a lot of people would like to know what she knows.
你給我聽好了
Now you listen to me very carefully.
不管你以為你拿到了什麼
Whatever you think you've got,
也不管你打算拿這些東西做什麼
whatever you intend to do with it,
我不會像格林那樣被敲詐牽著走
I don't respond to extortion the same way that Green does.
格林給你的許諾
What Green promised you,
我瞬間就可以抵消
that can be undone in a heartbeat.
所以才把你找來  確保不會變卦
And that's why you're here. Make sure it isn't.
你想要我的保護
You want my protection.
我不信任格林或聯調局的任何人
I don't trust Green or anyone at the Bureau.
還有誰知道
Who else knows about this?
沒人知道
No one.
我為什麼要相信你
Why should I trust you?
因為我們兩個都輸不起  夥計
'Cause we both have too much to lose, man.
穿上衣服
Get dressed.
你在幹什麼
What -- what are you doing here?
穿上衣服
Put some clothes on.
為什麼
Why -- why?
快點  我們走
Now. Let's go.
有人聯繫你嗎
Did anyone contact you?
你要帶我去哪
Where are you taking me?
回答我的問題
Answer my question.
沒人聯繫我
No. Nobody.
有人知道了我們的事
There's someone who knows about us.
知道你在哪
Who knows where you are.
知道我們什麼時候見過面
And when we've met.
你是不是要傷害我
Are you gonna hurt me?
你和我說實話就什麼事都不會有
Nothing's going to happen if you tell the truth.
我在說實話  沒有任何人聯繫我
I am. I -- I haven't been contacted by anybody.
別再撒謊了  瑞秋
Stop lying, Rachel.
你讓我幹什麼都行
I will do whatever you want.
求你別傷害我
Please, just don't hurt me.
我想讓你回答我的問題
What I want is for you to answer my questions,
這樣我才能幫你
so I can help you.
你一直以來都在毀掉我的生活
All you have ever done is fuck up my life.
你毀了團契的事
You fucked up the fellowship.
你毀了我和麗薩的感情
You fucked up what I had with Lisa.
即使我都按你說的做了
Even when I did what you asked.
你每次來找我都像變態一樣
And your sick fucking visits,
要我哄小孩似的給你讀書
and reading to you like a fucking child.
你有什麼毛病
What is wrong with you?
為什麼你就不能放了我
Why can't you just leave me be?
-為什麼你非要這麼  -住嘴
- Why do you have to be such a fucking -- - stop!
瑞秋  別做傻事
Rachel? Don't be stupid.
瑞秋
Rachel?
不會有事的
Everything's gonna be fine.
我做的一切都是想保護你
All I've ever done is try to protect you.
我現在也是想保護你
That's what I'm trying to do now.
你要相信我
You have to believe that.
我本來沒必要保護你
I didn't have to.
那樣事情會簡單得多
Been a lot easier if I didn't.
但我還是那樣做了  因為我...
But I did. I did it because I --
你幹什麼
What are you doing?
昨天我們結束了關於
Yesterday we completed hearings with regard to Articles
彈劾美國總統的聽證會
of Impeachment for the president of the United States.
主席現在開始聽取委員會動議
The chair will now entertain motions from the committee.
主席先生
Mr. Chairman.
主席請阿拉巴馬州議員發言
The chair recognizes the congressman from Alabama.
我建議我們直接開始對提議進行投票
I move that we put our recommendation directly to a vote
這樣眾議院435名成員
so that debate on this important matter may take place
都可以就此事進行辯論
on the House floor, open to all 435 members.
委員會有人反對跳過辯論階段嗎
Are there any objections to bypassing debate in this committee?
現在開始對是否將彈劾狀
We will now vote on recommendation of the Articles
送交眾議院投票進行表決
of Impeachment to the full House.
同意提議的請喊"贊成"
Those in favor of recommendation say, "Aye."
贊成
Aye.
反對者
Those opposed?
反對
Nay.
贊成佔多數
The ayes have it.
委員會正式建議眾議院
This committee officially recommends Articles
對彈劾狀進行投票
of Impeachment proceed to the House floor.
他來了
He's here.
副總統剛剛到達戴維營
The vice president is just arriving now here at Camp David.
重大新聞
副總統抵達戴維營
我們預計沃克總統
We except President Walker to speak within the hour,
會在一小時內宣佈
announcing his official resignation
辭去美國總統的職務
as president of the United States.
-你怎麼樣  -我還好
- How are you? - I'm fine.
總統先生
Mr. President.
我在廚房裏煮了咖啡
I have coffee in the kitchen.
-要來點嗎  -不用了
- Would you like some? - I'm fine.
你馬上就要成為
Well, you're about to become
自由世界最有權勢的人了
the most powerful man in the free world.
您沒必要這麼做  先生
You don't have to do this, sir.
我昨晚和科恩談過了
I spoke to Kern last night.
他不肯讓步
He's not gonna back down.
那我們就打敗他
So we'll beat him down.
不  弗蘭克
No, Frank.
我的支持率只剩8%了
My approvals are at eight percent.
即使我不被定罪  我也沒有領導國家的威儀了
Even if I avoid conviction, I have no mandate to lead.
所以我還是有尊嚴地下台
So better I step aside with some dignity
讓國家開始康復
so the nation can start to heal.
我永遠無法與您比肩  先生
I can never fill your shoes, sir.
你現在沒有選擇了
You don't have a choice now.
你的信
Your letter.
好了
Well,
我們去向大家引見美國第46任總統吧
shall we go introduce the 46th president of the United States?
總統先生收
自即日起
Effective immediately,
我辭去美國總統一職
I am resigning the presidency of the United States.
特莉莎和我認為這是最合適的辦法
Tricia and I believe that this is the best course of action,
既是為了我們和孩子
not only for us and our children,
更是為了這個國家
but for the country.
我無法否認  這對我們是不幸的一天
It's a sad day for us. I can't deny that.
但讓我心有慰藉的是
But I take solace in this:
弗蘭克·安德伍德將把美德  經驗
Frank Underwood will bring virtue, experience,
和勇氣帶入總統辦公室
and courage to the Oval Office.
由他擔任我的副總統  是我的榮幸
I have been blessed to have him as my vice president.
而有他這樣的朋友  更是我的幸運
But I'm even more blessed to call him my friend.
能夠擔任
It has been...
總統一職  服務國家
the greatest honor of my life
是我這一生無上的榮耀
to serve this country as president.
我感謝我的家人  白宮的工作人員
I thank my family, my staff,
以及所有那些支持我的人
and all of those who have supported me.
儘管最近幾個月風波不斷
Despite the last few months,
但我對祖國的信仰愈發堅定
my faith in this country has never been stronger.
上帝保佑你們
God bless all of you.
上帝保佑美利堅合眾國
And god bless the United States of America.
謝謝您的美言  總統先生
Thank you, Mr. President, for those words.
祝您好運  先生
Good luck to you, sir.
先生  請舉起右手  跟我宣誓
Sir, please raise your right hand and repeat after me.
本人  弗蘭西斯·J·安德伍德
I, Francis J. Underwood...
在此莊嚴宣誓
Do solemnly swear...
總統先生
Mr. President.
國務卿女士
Madam Secretary.
內閣其餘成員都在白宮等您
The rest of the Cabinet is awaiting you at the White House.
我們希望馬上為您做國家安全簡報  長官
We'd like to give you a national security briefing right away, sir.
詳情我都知道
I'm aware of the particulars.
請聯繫一下北京
Can you please get Beijing on the phone?
錢主席已經兩天沒回過總統的電話了
Qian hasn't returned the President's calls for two days.
現在總統換人了
Well, there's a new president now.
馬上給他打電話
Please get him on the line.
兩個小時前  作為三軍統帥
Two hours ago, President Underwood,
安德伍德總統下達了第一道命令
in his first act as commander in chief,
他要求第七艦隊撤出日本周邊海域
gave orders to the seventh fleet to vacate Japanese waters.
這得益於總統與錢主席進行的一次
This was a result of a productive conversation
頗有成效的對話
with President Qian,
而錢主席也對該海域的
who gave similar orders
中國艦隊下達了撤退的命令
to Chinese naval vessels in the same region.
他行動挺快啊
He moves quick.
你是說對中國人  還是對沃克
Do you mean with the Chinese or with Walker?
-馮先生  -怎麼了
- Mr. Feng? - What is it?
我們是司法部的  請隨我們走一趟
U.S. Justice Department. We need you to come with us.
-去哪  -你將被遣返回中國
- Where? - You're going back to China.
我申請了政治避難
I have asylum.
不  先生  你的避難請求已經被駁回了
No, sir, you don't. Your asylum has been rescinded.
我有書面證明  無條件無限期的庇護
I have it in writing. Unconditional and permanent.
先生  我說過了  對你的庇護已經作廢了
Sir, I'm telling you, your asylum has been rescinded.
請收拾個人物品  跟我們走
Now, please, gather your things and come with us.
駁回他的避難不是沒有後果的
Revoking his asylum will have consequences.
但是法律上沒問題吧
But we're solid from a legal perspective?
法律上沒問題  他的文件還沒進入批准流程
Legally yes. His initial paperwork hasn't been processed,
我們可以聲稱他對我國利益構成威脅
and we can claim he poses a threat to our national interests.
但這會削弱國務院的信譽
But it diminishes the integrity of our State Department.
哪一個更重要  凱茜  信譽還是和平
What's more important, Cathy? Integrity or peace?
你知道他會被處決的
You know they'll execute him.
中國人說對了一件事
The Chinese are right about one thing.
有時候  就得捨棄一人  保證全局
Sometimes you have to sacrifice the one for the many.
我們回華盛頓吧
Let's get back to Washington.
好的  請及時通知我  非常感謝
Okay. Please let me know. Thanks very much.
-有消息嗎  -還是沒有
- Anything? - Not yet.
你看看能不能通過戒酒互助會查到他的行蹤
See if you can track down anyone from his regular AA meetings.
我和輔導員談過了
I spoke to the moderator.
他說已經有好幾周沒見過道格了
He said he hasn't seen Doug in several weeks.
我查過醫院  問過他的房東
I checked all the hospitals, his landlord...
先生  人都到齊了
Sir, everyone's here.
好  等手頭事一過
All right, when this is all over
你和南茜一起找道格
I want you to work with Nancy on finding Doug.
我已經和特區警察局打過招呼
I've already alerted the D.C. Metro.
他們會對他的車牌發佈全境通告
They put out an APB on his car.
我們會找到他的  先生
We'll find him, sir.
克萊爾呢
Claire?
就在外面
Just outside.
咱們走  南茜
Let's go, Nancy.
女士們先生們
Ladies and gentleman,
有請總統先生和第一夫人
the President and the first lady.
弗蘭西斯
Francis,
我知道離你生日還有段時間
I know your birthday isn't for a couple weeks,
但我要送你一份禮物
but I got you something.
-這是幹什麼  -打開嘛
- What's this? - Open it.
我讓人新做了一個
I had a new one made.
我愛你
I love you.
我也愛你
I love you, too.
你進去吧
You go ahead.
一起來吧
Come on.
這是我們共同努力的結果
We earned this together.
你先自己去  好好享受一下
Take a few moments for yourself first.
我就在外面
I'll be out here.
1789年4月21日  美國第一任副總統約翰·亞當斯在紐約宣誓就職時
當選總統喬治·華盛頓還在趕往臨時首都的路上
直到4月30日才正式就任  所以在30日之前的9天裏
亞當斯作為副總統就成了這個年輕國家的最高行政長官
美國是先有有副總統  後有總統的
美國歷史上  曾有9位副總統因總統亡故或辭職而接任成為總統
1973年  美國副總統阿格紐因貪腐被調查而被迫辭職
來自密西根州的眾議員福特被時任總統的尼克松任命為副總統
次年  尼克松因水門事件被迫辭職  福特成為美國第38任總統
福特未經民主選舉就擔任過副總統和總統的職位